tutitalia.com 2016-06-08

# TutITALIA - Privacy policy

TutITALIA.COM ("TutITALIA ", "we", "our", "us") and its subsidiary companies respect the privacy rights of its online visitors ("you", "your", "yours") and recognize the importance of protecting the information collected about them. We have adopted a Privacy Policy that guides how we collect, store and use the information that you provide us with.

If you are under 18, we require that you inform a parent or guardian about TutITALIA's Privacy Policy and [Terms and Conditions](http://tutitalia.com/terms_and_conditions_info) as well as requiring their consent to the Privacy Policy and [Terms and Conditions](http://tutitalia.com/terms_and_conditions_info) before registering with TutITALIA or placing and order with TutITALIA.

The following information is provided by TutITALIA to enable our online visitors to be fully informed of our Privacy Policies. By visiting TutITALIA.COM, you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this Privacy Policy and the [Terms and Conditions](http://tutitalia.com/terms_and_conditions_info).

Please note that this policy applies to TutITALIA and/or its subsidiaries, but not to websites maintained by other companies or organizations to which we link. Please ensure that you read the Privacy Policy of such other companies or organizations before submitting any personal information. Furthermore, from time to time TutITALIA may employ third party business partners to collect personal information on TutITALIA's behalf. In such cases, these third parties will be subject to confidentiality agreements and instructed by TutITALIA to fully comply with the TutITALIA Privacy Policy as set forth herein.

**EXACTLY WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION MAY BE COLLECTED ABOUT YOU AND BY WHAT MEANS?**

TutITALIA collects personal information in several ways directly from its online visitors when they order for themselves, or when they register for a service offered by TutITALIA. If an order is placed with us, we need to hold personal information including your name, email address, phone numbers, home address, shipping address(es), credit card billing address(es) so that we can process and fulfil your orders. Credit card details are entered directly into MonetaWeb of INTESA SANPAOLO bank systems and are neither transmitted nor held on TutITALIA systems. In certain instances we may be required to collect and store additional data including credit card details. This will only be done with your explicit consent. Additionally we may also obtain information as a result of authentication or identity checks. Sometimes we may ask for your telephone number. This number may be given to our courier for delivery services. These details allow us to process your order and to let you know the status of your order.

**OTHER INFORMATION WE COLLECT THROUGH OUR SERVICES**

As a user of our services, we may collect non-personal data about use of the website, such as pages visited, times and volume of use of the services as well as Traffic Data. Traffic data includes logs, details of networks, time of log-on or access, length of sessions and similar systems data.

**WHAT ABOUT COOKIES?**

Our site uses cookies to keep track of how often you visit our site, the contents of your shopping cart, previous purchases and to deliver content specific to your interests. (A cookie is a piece of information that is stored on your computer's hard drive by your web browser which tracks your movements within websites.) Most browsers are automatically set to accept cookies but usually you can alter the settings of your browser to prevent automatic acceptance. If you choose not to receive cookies, you may still use most of the features of our website, including the ability to purchase items.

**HOW THIS INFORMATION MAY BE USED, INCLUDING ANYONE IT MIGHT BE SHARED WITH**

TutITALIA may use your personal information for the processing of orders, payments and to provide you with a personalized shopping experience. We will also use your details to fulfil and deliver your orders and manage your account. Your personal information may also be checked with credit agencies to prevent fraud. Where there is a legal obligation to do so, we may disclose your information to any relevant regulatory body.

When you register with TutITALIA, you will be asked if you want to subscribe to our update service. If you choose to opt-in for this service, the information you provide will allow us to alert you to new products, features and enhancements; special offers; upgrade opportunities; contests and events of interest. Similarly, if you choose to opt-in for this service, from time-to-time we will use the information you provide to promote the products and services of our business partners. We do collate statistical information about site traffic, sales and other commercial information which we may pass on to trusted third parties but these statistics do not include any information which can identify you personally. We see this as a value-added service helping you to find useful products or services. We strive to limit use of your information to those offers that we think you would appreciate receiving. Finally, we may use your personal information for our internal marketing and demographic studies, together with non-personal data to monitor customer patterns so we can consistently improve our site design to better meet our visitors' needs. If we change our policy on disclosure to others, we will inform you and give you the choice of opting out.

**OPT-IN AND OPT-OUT PROVISION**

When you register, we will provide a link to the [Terms and Conditions](http://tutitalia.com/terms_and_conditions_info) and consent button for the collection of your personal data.

At all times, we will offer you the opportunity to opt-out of any service to which you have subscribed. Any e-mail we send you will contain an easy automated opt-out link so that you can opt-out of that particular mailshot. Simply follow the indications in the e-mail. In particular, you can opt-out from having your personally identifiable information shared with our business partners or TutITALIA's subsidiaries (except as required by law, court order, or as requested by other government or law enforcement authority or as may be required to deliver your purchases). It is not the Company's current policy to share its customers' personal details with third parties other than as stated herein.

Should you choose to have your name and personal data removed from our database all together, you can do so by sending an e-mail to tutitalia@tutitalia.com or by writing to us at: DELIS PRO, Via Ugo Foscolo 79/C, 47854 Montescudo (RN), Italy.

**How You Can Access And, If Necessary, Change Your Personal Information Maintained By TutITALIA**

If for any reason you are concerned that the personal information maintained by TutITALIA is not correct, please visit the web site and, after logging into the site using the "Login" menu on the home page; your personal information will be made available for review and change in the "My Account" section. Only you, and/or upon request from you, the Customer Care department can access your personal data from the website using your password and User ID. Information may be changed online within Personal Details, & Shipping Details, If you prefer to contact us by e-mail at tutitalia@tutitalia.com, we will amend your personal details.

**SAFEGUARDING YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION**

We will only collect personally identifiable information to the extent deemed reasonably necessary to serve you in view of our legitimate business purposes as set out above, and we will use our best endeavors to maintain appropriate safeguards to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of the information you have provided us with. When you place an order or access your account information, we use a Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption which encrypts your information before it is sent to us to protect it from unauthorized use. In addition, we will take reasonable steps to ensure that third party business partners to whom we transfer any data will provide sufficient protection of that personal information.

**WHERE AND HOW TO ASK QUESTIONS OR FILE COMPLAINTS**

If you require further information about our Privacy Policy, please go to the help section of the web site where frequently asked questions (FAQ's) are answered, if you require more information please go to the Contact Us section of the web site and send us an email.

**YOUR CONSENT**

By visiting TutITALIA.COM, you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this Privacy Policy and the [Terms and Conditions](http://tutitalia.com/terms_and_conditions_info).
